Grandma
奶奶
Miss Jiang is really a rumored symbol
蒋小姐真是传闻般的标志啊
Do you still adapt after returning home
回国后还适应吗
Is there anything we can do for you
有什么事情需要我们帮忙的
You can talk to Xiaofeng
你尽管找小枫说
There is really a grandmother. Since she doesn't treat me like an outsider,
还真有 奶奶既然不把我当外人
Then I'll be straight with it
那我就直说了
Okay, you tell me quickly
好好 你快讲讲
There is nothing else
倒也没有别的
Is our Wonderland culture
就是咱们奇境文化
It is said that it is the most concerned employee in the industry
说是业内最关心员工
It is also an enterprise that advocates hierarchical management
也是提倡等级化管理的企业
So I suggest
所以呢我建议
Our annual leave can be increased to one month
咱们的年假可以把时长提升到1个月
Then give some shuttle buses to employees who live far away
然后给住的远的员工呢配一些班车
Besides, the ladies' room in our company is always in line
还有呀咱们公司的女厕所总是排队
There are no people in the men's room
男厕所都没什么人的
Can you add a little more ladies' room
可不可以多加一点女厕所呀
Oops
哎呀
Am I saying too much
我是不是说太多了
Miss Jiang, it seems
蒋小姐 看来呀
You are quite familiar with our company
你对我们公司挺熟悉啊
Show her around
带她参观过
Thank you, Miss Jiang, for your concern
感谢蒋小姐的关心啊
Should
应该的
Fast Southern Wind
快快 楠风
Have you written down everything Miss Jiang said just now
刚才蒋小姐说的事情你都记下了没有
If it can't be solved well, I'll settle accounts with you
解决不好我可要找你算账了哦
Miss Jiang's dish today
蒋小姐今天的菜
They are all specially prepared according to your preferences
都是特意按照你的喜好准备的
Your uncle Liu also specially asked for us
你刘叔叔也是特意帮我们问到的
Come and try it
来 你尝尝
How could I forget
我怎么忘了
Xizhou loves to eat this kind of thing that can kill me in one bite
希舟就爱吃这种一口就能要我命的东西
It's a big deal to go to the hospital
大不了进医院
Xiaofeng, pay attention
小枫你注意点呗
The waiter changed the plate
服务员换一盘
Give him a new suit
给他换一套新衣服
I usually drop a drop of oil on my body
平常身上滴下一滴油
People who need to take three baths
就要洗3次澡的人
Why are you so careless today
今天怎么这么不小心
How do you know
你怎么知道
Don't thank the money for clothes. Let the finance deduct it from your salary
不用谢衣服的钱让财务从你工资里扣
I am very happy today
今天我特别的高兴
Everybody raise your glasses
大家举杯
I hope our Xu family will have many happy events this year
我希望我们徐家今年喜事连连啊
Everybody drink
大家喝
Xi Zhou is old enough to drink. I have to maintain her personnel
希舟酒量老好了我得把她人事维持住
Afflictive
难受
Elder sister
大姐
Thanks to you, it's only 200 meters away from the hotel now
托您的福现在开出酒店才没200米
Dude, it's okay
哥们 没事啊
You drive yours
你开你的
I threw up when I opened the window
我开窗就吐了
You still feel proud, don't you
你还觉得自己挺骄傲是吗
Now get off and take a taxi back
现在下车自己打车回去
Drive
开车
I'm telling you
我告诉你
You mustn't bully Jiang Xizhou
你不许欺负蒋希舟
She's the best
她是最好的
I bullied her
我欺负她
It's right for me to bully you
我欺负你才对啊
Right
对
You're bullying me
你欺负的是我
Why are you looking for a cell phone
你找手机干嘛
I want to ask my boss for leave
我要跟老板请假
I am your boss
我就是你老板
Boss
老板
I would like to take a leave of absence
我想请个假
Sure
好啊
Then you beg me
那你求求我